A Guide to the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter, Rotary Club Records, 1965-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter, Rotary Club Records, 1965-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2012-076
0.3 cu. ft. 1 box
The Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter, Rotary Club Records contains newspaper articles, brochures, handouts, pamphlets and flyers pertaining to the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Rotary Club from 1965 to 1998.
Rotary Club (Christiansburg-Blacksburg, Va.).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter, Rotary Club Records was acquired by Special Collections prior to 2009.
Historical Note
The Rotary Club of Christiansburg and Blacksburg was founded in 1923 as a service club. Its objectives were to provide a network for its members, learn about and service the Christiansburg and Blacksburg communities, and fund programs and scholarship programs in and around Montgomery County. The chapter is part of the larger organization Rotary International. The chapter is still active today.
Scope and Content
The collection includes records and memorabilia from the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter of the Rotary Club. In addition to administrative materials like the constitution and by-laws, there are clippings and articles about the club, histories, and pamphlets and publications from events.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into folders by material type.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Rotary Club (Christiansburg-Blacksburg, Va.).
Subjects:
Blacksburg (Va.); Local/Regional History and Appalachian South
Geographical Names:
Christiansburg, Va.
Contents List
- Clippings and Articles, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 1-1)
- Constitution and By-Laws (Box-folder 1-2)
- "The First Fifty Years of the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Rotary Club" (Box-folder 1-3)
- "History of the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Chapter" Micheal Kipps (Box-folder 1-4)
- History of the 75th District Rotary International (Box-folder 1-5)
- The Rotary Club Nominates Dr. A.A. Showalter for Governor, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 1-7)
- Town of Blacksburg Charter (Box-folder 1-8)
- "Welcome to Rotary" Charter Night to Honor the Christiansburg-Blacksburg Rotary Club, 1979 (Box-folder 1-9)
- 75th Chapter Anniversary, 1998 (Box-folder 1-10)
- 75th District Annual Conference Pamphlets, 1970-1991 (Box-folder 1-11)